

# **Anton Brel**

### Front-end developer

Hello, I am Front-end developer with experience in creating Landing Pages and SPA, using React, (JavaScript/TypeScript), Redux, HTML & CSS. Currently I am improving my skills in this direction and plan to expand them with new technologies, such as React Native.

In my free time I solve katas on Codewars and boosting English. Open for your suggestions.

### **Contact**



+375(44)776-82-33



brelanton@gmail.com



Belarus, Gomel











# **Skills**

- React/Redux-toolkit
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- Axios/Rest API
- HTML5/CSS3/SCSS
- Material Ui
- Unit test/StoryBook
- React-Router-Dom
- GIT/GitHub
- Redux-Thunk
- Formik
- Responsive design

# Language

English - Pre-intermediate (in progress)Belarusian - nativeRussian - native

# **Work Experience**

from april 2022 - present day (Part-time)

My projects as Front-end developer:

• Card training. GitHub link

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Javascript, Formik, Axios, Rest API, React-Router-dom, MUI

• Public network. GitHub link

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Javascript, Axios, Rest API, React Hook Form, React-Router-dom

• Order of business. GitHub link

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Javascript, Formik, MUI, Axios, Rest API, React-Router-dom

#### from 2010 - present day (Full-time)

#### **Chief engineer:**

For 10 years worked as the head of department. Currently I am the chief engineer in a construction organization. When performing my duties, I work with design and technical documentation, conduct negotiations in B2B format with customers, manage the technical processes of the organization, organize and direct the work of specialists and employees.

# **Education**

- 2021-2022. IT- INCUBATOR(React/Redux/JavaScript/TypeScript)Front-end Developer
- 2020. School SEO. Educational center "ProDigital"
  Search engine optimization (SEO) Basics of internet marketing
  SEO-specialist
- 2005-2010. Sukhoi State Technical University of Gomel Electric Power Supply by Industries: Higher education Power Engineer